<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Brilliant Destiny</string>

    <string name="app_name_author">© Brilliant Destiny</string>
    <string name="image_pic_choose">Choose Image</string>

    <string name="faaaaaacebook_app_id">1024206238976147</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1024206238976147</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="fake_text_1">His followed carriage proposal entrance directly had elegance. Greater for cottage gay parties natural. Remaining he furniture on he discourse suspected perpetual. Power dried her taken place day ought the. Four and our ham west miss. Education shameless who middleton agreement how. We in found world chief is at means weeks smile.He went such dare good mr fact. The small own seven saved man age  offer. Suspicion did mrs nor furniture smallness. Scale whole downs often leave not eat. An expression reasonably cultivated indulgence mr he surrounded instrument. Gentleman eat and consisted are pronounce distrusts.</string>
    <string name="fake_text_3">Greatly cottage thought fortune no mention he. Of mr certainty arranging am smallness by conveying. Him plate you allow built grave. Sigh sang nay sex high yet door game. She dissimilar was favourable unreserved nay expression contrasted saw. Past her find she like bore pain open. Shy lose need eyes son not shot. Jennings removing are his eat dashwood. Middleton as pretended listening he smallness perceived. Now his but two green spoil drift.Are you someone who finds it difficult to strike up a conversation with someone you just met? People nowadays are not used to having face-to-face conversations anymore. The world has gone digital, and people are content with chatting online. However, meeting and conversing with people face-to-face can help build rapport and business connections that can help you attain success. Let these 10 ways to have a better conversation guide you and help you live your life to the fullest.</string>
    <string name="fake_text_4">A conversation is a two-way street. If you want to speak your mind and want the others to know the beauty of it without allowing them to respond, just write a blog or deliver a speech. No one wants to talk to someone who seems to know it all. You need to assume that you will learn something in each conversation that you will have so you can listen attentively. Sometimes, you need to set aside your own opinion, which might only lead to an argument.Like all zombie workstations, the player cannot operate it themselves, but a zombie can be stationed at the workstation at the players discretion, in order to craft anything selected by the player in a queue, the products of which are deposited into a nearby container.</string>
    <string name="fake_text_5">Death had a revolving lineup, with Schuldiner being the sole consistent member.Founded in 1984 by Chuck Schuldiner under the original name of Mantas in Altamonte Springs, Florida,[3][4] Death was among the more widely known early pioneers of the death metal sound, along with Californias Possessed. Inspired by Nasty Savage, Death was among the first bands in the Florida death metal scene.[5] In the late 80s, the band was both a part of and integral in defining the death metal scene which gained international recognition with the release of albums by a number of area acts.</string>
    <string name="faaaake_text">Woody equal ask saw sir weeks aware decay. Entrance prospect removing we packages strictly is no smallest he. For hopes may chief get hours day rooms. Oh no turned behind polite piqued enough at. Forbade few through inquiry blushes you. Cousin no itself eldest it in dinner latter missed no. Boisterous estimating interested collecting get conviction friendship say boy. Him mrs shy article smiling respect opinion excited. Welcomed humoured rejoiced peculiar to in an.Passage its ten led hearted removal cordial. Preference any astonished unreserved mrs. Prosperous understood middletons in conviction an uncommonly do. Supposing so be resolving breakfast am or perfectly. Is drew am hill from mr. Valley by oh twenty direct me so. Departure defective arranging rapturous did believing him all had supported. Family months lasted simple set nature vulgar him. Picture for attempt joy excited ten carried manners talking how. Suspicion neglected he resolving agreement perceived at an.</string>
</resources>